https://www.ingeniumsw.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
No menu assigned!
Ingenium
Software Privacy Policy
1. Introduction.  Ingenium Software, Inc., on behalf of itself and its
affiliates, (together, “Ingenium” or “we” or
“us”) is the operator of this Site (as defined in Ingenium Software’s
Terms of Use (the “Terms”). We know privacy is important to you; it
is also vital to our business. This Privacy Policy describes the types of
“Personal Information” (information that is identifiable to a
particular person) that Ingenium Software collects (directly or through service
providers) in connection with this Site, and how that Personal Information is
used, shared and protected. This Privacy Policy is considered part of the
Terms.
2. Minors.
We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from or about individuals under 18 years of age.   Please do not submit such information to us, and as a parent or legal guardian, please do not allow your children to submit personal information without your permission.
3. Cookies, Browser Information and Related Issues.
a.
When you visit the Site, we may receive certain standard information that your
browser sends to every website you visit, such as the originating IP address,
browser type and language, access times and referring website addresses, and other
such information. This data may be used, among other reasons, to improve the
operation and security of the Site by assisting in “authenticating”
who you are when you access this Site, particularly if you register for access
to part of the Site and are issued or create a username and password. We may
receive additional technical data about the device used to access the Site
(“Device Data”) (such as device ID, device model, operating system
version, application types and versions, browser type, language, and plug-ins,
originating IP address, and time zone and geolocation information).
Device Data may be used as part of our security controls to uniquely identify
the device and authenticate the user when accessing the Site. Device Data may
be shared (along with information about any fraudulent transactions using the
device) with one or more third-party service providers. These providers will
compare and add the Device Data and fraud data to a database of similar device
and fraud information in order to identify and block access to the Site by
devices associated with fraudulent or abusive activity.  We will not share
with service providers any information that personally identifies the user of
the device.
b.
We may receive additional information about your visit to the Site, including
the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take in
connection with the Site and any products and services offered through it. This
data may be used, among other reasons, to improve the operation of the Site.
c.
Like most websites, the Site also uses “cookies,” which are small
data files placed on your computer or other device by the Web server when you
visit the Site. Most such cookies are “session” cookies that are only
used while you are on the Site, but a few are “persistent” cookies
that stay on your hard drive and are read by the Web server when you return to
the Site. The Site uses cookies to recognize your device and to store your
preferences and other information on your device. This saves you time by eliminating
the need to repeatedly enter the same information and will display your
personalized content on your later visits to the Site. Cookies cannot and will
not be used to deliver or run programs on your device. Most Web browsers
automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to
decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign
in or use other interactive features of the Site that depend on cookies.
d.
You may encounter our cookies or pixel tags on websites that we do not
control.  For example, if you view a Web page created by a third party or
use an application developed by a third party, they may place a cookie or pixel
tag on your computer or device.
e.
Widgets: Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like
button, and Widgets, such as the Share this button, or interactive
mini-programs.  These Features may collect your IP address, which page you
are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function
properly.  Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third
party or hosted directly on our Site.  Your interactions with these
Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
f.
Tracking: With respect to personally identifiable information about an
individual’s online activities over time and across different Web sites or
online services, when a consumer uses this Site, except as required by law: (1)
parties other than the operator of this Site are not permitted to collect such
information, and (2) the operator of this Site does not collect such
information (except information reasonably necessary to process and document
user transactions).  Therefore, this Site has no need to respond to and
does not respond to Web browser “do not track” signals or other
mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice regarding the collection of
such information.
4. What Types of “Personal Information” We Collect,
and How We Collect, Use and Disclose It.  In addition to the types of information
described in section 3 above, we may also collect Personal Information about
you when you directly submit it to us. Ingenium Software may provide you the
opportunity to do such things as subscribe to email alerts regarding Ingenium
Software events or company news, to request company information, or to request
product or service information through an email contact form. Such information
may include your name, your company’s name, your personal or company email
address or other contact information.  It is up to you whether to provide
this information.  Such information will be used and disclosed as
reasonably necessary to meet your needs and respond to your requests, such as
disclosing it to our email service provider to send you emails or to one of our
affiliated entities to provide you with product information. Parties with whom
we share Personal Information are bound to contracts requiring them to use and
disclose the information only for the permitted purposes and to use reasonable
security measures to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access and
use. Ingenium Software may also use and disclose Personal Information to comply
with laws, regulations, court orders and lawful instructions from government
agencies, to protect the personal safety of Site users or the public, to
prevent and defend claims, to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems, to
enforce the Terms, and to protect our rights and property.  If you
register for a service offered through the Site, Ingenium Software may collect
additional Personal Information and use it for additional purposes reasonably
related to that service.
5. How We Protect Personal Information About You. To protect Personal
Information about you from unauthorized access and use, Ingenium Software maintains
physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards, and requires those to whom we
disclose Personal Information (including our employees and service providers
that assist us in operating this Site) to do the same. You can update your Personal
Information by clicking “Support Portal” and signing into your
account.
6. Keeping Up to Date with Our Privacy Policy. Ingenium Software
may amend this Policy at any time by posting a revised version on this Site,
which will be effective at the time it is posted for all Personal Information
collected thereafter unless a delayed effective date is expressly stated in the
revision. By using this Site after such additions or modifications are posted,
you are agreeing to accept and comply with the Policy as modified.
7. Scope.
a. Supplemental Privacy Policies.  Some areas,
features and services on the Site may be offered on the condition that you view
and agree to privacy terms and disclosures specific to those areas, features
and services.  Those specific privacy terms and disclosures will be deemed
to supplement the terms and disclosures in this Privacy Policy and, if
inconsistent, to supersede them.
b. Other Ingenium Software Sites. This Privacy Policy
is applicable to this Site, as specified above. However, an Other Ingenium
Software Site may have its own privacy policy or other privacy-related terms
posted. As with the Terms, those other privacy terms and conditions shall
apply to privacy-related issues regarding that Other Ingenium Software Site and
the use of any services, functionalities or other offerings made in connection
with that Other Ingenium Software Site, and this Privacy Policy shall not apply
in such circumstances. This Privacy Policy also does not apply to any websites Ingenium
Software creates for any individual client; such websites shall be subject to
the terms and conditions set forth in the applicable agreement between Ingenium
Software and that client.
c. Links to Third-Party Sites.  This Site may
provide links to other sites operated by third parties over whom Ingenium
Software has no control and whose privacy policies may differ from ours. These
links are provided for your convenience. If you browse on or submit Personal
Information to any of those sites, information about you may be collected by
them and will be governed by their privacy policies.
NAVIGATIONHOME
PRODUCTS
etherFAX
etherFAX SEN
etherFAX A2E
etherFAX DR
etherFAX Toolkit
FaxCore
RightFax® Support Policy Changes
ABOUT INGENIUM SOFTWARE Ingenium is a trusted Strategic Solutions Provider for global voice, fax, secure email and cloud computing services.
We are extremely passionate about what we do and who we serve. We consider ourselves an extension of your IT or Business Team when it comes to solving your needs.
Ingenium markets our fax transport services thru our faxserver.net brand.
Copyright © Ingenium Software.
All Rights Reserved.
